rechargetricks.in 2018-12-23

# Privacy Policy | RechargeTricks.in, Free Recharge Tricks, Deals

###### Privacy Policy

 _ **What do we use your information?**_

Yes, Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

1) To personalize your experience, ( your information helps us to better).

2) To improve our website  
( we continually improve our website offerings based ).

3) To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site features.

 ** _Cookies:-_**

Cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Awesome Motive uses cookies to help Awesome Motive identify and track visitors, their usage of Awesome Motive website, and their website access preferences. Awesome Motive visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Awesome Motive’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Awesome Motive’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

 ** _Advertising:-_**

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Awesome Motive and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

 ** _Sharing your Personal information:-_**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising or other uses.

 _ **Third Party Links:-**_

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

 ** _Online Privacy  Policy Only:-_**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

 ** _Your Consent:-_**

By using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy.

 ** _Changes to our Privacy Policy:-_**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, this is your responsibility to check this page time to time.

 ** _Contacting us:-_**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may [Contact us](http://rechargetricks.in/contact-us) using the information below.

<http://rechargetricks.in/contact-us>
